agrilife.org 2019-11-23

# State Links and Policies

### State Resources

### Texas A&M University Links

### Privacy & Security Policy

The web page you have been viewing was developed by the Texas A&M AgriLife unit of the Texas A&M University System. As such, it maintains this site as a public service. The following is the privacy policy for this site:

We do not use cookies to collect information. Note: A cookie file contains unique information a website can use to track such things as passwords, lists of pages you’ve visited, and the date when you last looked at a specific page or to identify your session at a particular website. A cookie is often used in commercial sites to identify the items selected for a specific shopping cart application.

If you send us an electronic mail message with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, or fill out a form that emails us this information, we will only use the personally identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question.

For site management functions, information is collected for analysis and statistical purposes. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to any outside parties unless legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal actions.  We may collect and set information to track marketing to sales processes, but this will not include Personally Identifiable Information unless explicitly noted.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your use of this Website, please contact the Webmaster or through regular mail at:

Texas A&M AgriLife  
AgriLife Communications Department  
Attention: Webmaster  
578 John Kimbrough Blvd.  
2112 TAMU  
College Station, TX 77843-2112

We use log analysis tools to create summary statistics, which are used for purposes such as assessing what information is of most interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. The following information is collected for this analysis:

  * User Client hostname – The hostname (or IP address if DNS is disabled) of the user/client requesting access.
  * HTTP header, “user-agent” – The user-agent information includes the type of browser, its version, and the operating system it is running on.
  * HTTP header, “referrer” – The referrer specifies the page from which the client accessed the current page.
  * System date – The date and time of the user/client request.
  * Full request – The exact request the user/client made.
  * Status – The status code the server returned to the user/client.
  * Content length – The content length, in bytes, of the document sent to the user/client.
  * Method – The request methods used.
  * Universal Resource Identifier (URI) – The location of a resource on the server.
  * Query string of the URI – Anything after the question mark in a URI.
  * Protocol – The transport protocol and version used.

### Information Security

We employ extensive security measures consistent with the Texas Administrative Code (TAC) “Information Security Standards” and Texas A&M University Rules and Standard Administrative Procedures to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or destruction of information under our control, as well as the loss, misuse, or alteration of our websites and/or associated electronic information resources. The information resources that support our websites undergo an annual information security risk assessment via the Information Security Awareness Assessment and Compliance (ISAAC) system. The ISAAC system assesses the security posture of information systems and measures compliance with information security standards.
